## **JULIUS OGUNNIYI**

22, Bolarin Street, Off Pab Bustop, Ikotun-Egbe, Lagos, Nigeria. +2349024420929
ogunniyi.julius12@gmail.com · https://ng.linkedin.com/in/julius-ogunniyi-97884b199 ·
https://myportfolio-murex.vercel.app/port.html

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Newly graduated self-motivated Web Developer with comprehensive experience of 2 years of developing websites. Passionate and hardworking to deliver dynamic interfaces and clean code on deadlines, strong in HTML, CSS and JavaScript programmer and also WordPress template creation.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Makintouch Consulting - System Administrator/Junior Web Developer March 2020 - October 2020.

- Configured, tested and maintained network equipment.
- Planned and implemented upgrades to system hardware and software.
- Resolved issues and escalated problems with knowledgeable support and quality service.
- Worked with users to determine areas in need of improvement.
- Implemented, maintained, developed and tested the installation and update of file servers, print servers and application servers in all departments.
- I was also working with the senior full stack developer and learning web design.
- Worked on the organization website with wordpress, developed some basic websites using HTML, CSS and Bootstrap.

# Freelance - Front End Developer June 2021 – January 2022.

- Converted User Interface designs into functional web applications
- Worked with a team of Mobile App Engineers and Back End Engineer to achieve a project.
- Worked with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Jquery.

## Makintouch Consulting – Front End Developer Feb 2022 – Present.

- Created custom websites by harnessing HTML, CSS, and JavaScript skills.
- Improved website navigation with clear and intuitive UX mapping.

- Integrated Flutterwave third party platform API with a website.
- Designed web pages to enhance branding and navigation.
- Designed graphics with Adobe Creative Cloud to achieve brand goals.
- Boosted website performance and stability through planned maintenance and targeted troubleshooting.

### **CERTIFICATES OF TRAINING**

- Web Development HIIT PLC (July August, 2019).
- CompTIA A+ (September, 2020).
- AWS

## **EDUCATION**

## **Academic Qualifications**

- **Bowen University, Iwo, Osun state** B.Sc. In Computer Science and Information Technology (**September, 2017 November 2021**).
- Lagos State Senior Model College, Badore, Ajah, Lagos West Africa Senior School Certificate Examination (June 2017).

## **SKILLS**

- Website optimisation
- Adobe Creative Cloud
- Graphics Design
- HTML coding
- WordPress
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Jquery
- UI/UX design
- Web development projects
- GitHub

## LANGUAGES SPOKEN

• English, Yoruba.

### **INTERESTS**

- Coding
- Music
- Video games

#### **REFERENCES**

• Available on request.